JESSIE COLEMAN

Decatur GA · (915) 831 9109 Jessiecoleman928@gmail.com

Upcoming fourth year student at Emory University. Experienced with working with Agile/Scrum as well as OpenAI API, React JS, OOP programming, web design, app design, and game development.

EXPERIENCE

JUN 2023 - PRESENT

SWE INTERN PUBLICIS SAPIENT

Frontend/backend software engineer intern for popular retail corporation. Used React JS as well as ChatGPT API.

AUG 2022 - PRESENT

EMORY COMPUTER SCIENCE LAB STAFF

My responsibilities include tutoring computer science students, computer repair, and computer maintenance.

MAY 2022 - AUG 2022

BEST BUY COMPUTER REPAIR

My job was to diagnose and fix software/hardware problems with clients' computers, as well as smartphones and tablets.

EDUCATION

MAY 2019

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, FRANKLIN HIGH SCHOOL

JUNE 2020-PRESENT

COMPUTER SCIENCE BS, EMORY UNIVERSITY

SKILLS

- Java/C#/C
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript

- Python/Lua
- Unity/Android Studio/Arduino
- React JS/OpenAl API

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- Online multiplayer tank game with WebGL. https://sacredstudios.itch.io/chidi-tanks-03-alpha
- Visualization of A* pathfinding algorithm using Arduino
- Website using CSS/JavaScript/HTML.

- Full game/sprites for 2D game with Unity
- Generative math quiz using ChatGPT and React IS
- Animated poster using Android Studio.